<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="tos_title">Terms of Services</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to Num Sum!</string>
    <string name="connection_title">Connect the Apps</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="agree_and_proceed">Agree and Proceed</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="terms_of_services"><![CDATA[## Terms of Service for Num Sum\n\n**PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF SERVICE (\"TERMS\") CAREFULLY. BY DOWNLOADING, ACCESSING OR USING THE CALL SYNC AND/OR NUM SUM APPLICATIONS (\"APPS\"), YOU (\"YOU\" OR \"USER\") AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT DOWNLOAD, ACCESS, OR USE THE APPS.**\n\n**1. Introduction**\n\nThese Terms constitute a legally binding agreement between you and the developer of Call Sync and Num Sum, mobile applications that allow for the synchronization and storage of call history between Android devices (\"Services\").\n\n**2. Description of Services**\n\n2.1 Call Sync and Num Sum work together to provide call history synchronization. Num Sum, installed on the primary device, periodically checks for new call history, encrypts it, and uploads it to a secure cloud database (Firebase Firestore). Call Sync, installed on a secondary device, periodically downloads, decrypts, and displays this call history.\n\n2.2 Both Apps require user authentication through Firebase Authentication to access and use the Services.\n\n**3. User Data and Privacy**\n\n3.1 **Data Collection:** The Apps collect and process the following user data:\n    * **Call History:**  Num Sum collects and encrypts your call history (including phone numbers, contact name, call duration, and timestamps).\n    * **User Behavior Data:** Both Apps collect data on how you interact with them, including usage patterns, feature access, and performance metrics, using Firebase Analytics. This data is anonymized to the extent possible. \n    * **Device Information:**  The Apps collect information about your device, including model, operating system, and unique identifiers.\n\n3.2 **Data Usage:** We use the collected data for the following purposes:\n    * **Providing and improving the Services:**  To enable call history synchronization, troubleshoot issues, and enhance app functionality.\n    * **Analytics and Research:** To analyze app usage trends, improve user experience, and develop new features.\n    * **Personalized Advertising:**  The Apps display advertisements using Google AdMob, which may collect and use data to personalize ad content. \n\n3.3 **Data Security:**\n    * We use industry-standard encryption (provided by Firebase) to protect your call history during transmission and storage.\n    * Access to data stored on Firebase Firestore is restricted to authorized personnel and protected by Firebase security rules.\n\n3.4 **Data Sharing:** We do not share your personal data with third parties except:\n    * **Service Providers:**  We may engage trusted third-party service providers to assist us in providing and improving the Services (e.g., Firebase for data storage and authentication, Google AdMob for advertising). These providers are obligated to protect your data.\n    * **Legal Compliance:** We may disclose your data if required by law or to comply with a valid legal process (e.g., a court order or subpoena). **While we strive to cooperate with legitimate legal requests, please be aware that we cannot decrypt the content of your call history due to the encryption method employed. You are solely responsible for complying with any legal obligations related to providing access to your call history data.**\n\n3.5 **Data Retention:**  We retain your call history data in Firebase Firestore for as long as you maintain an active account with the Apps. **To minimize potential security risks, call history data is deleted from Firebase Firestore once it has been successfully downloaded by the Call Sync app.** You can delete your call history data by signing out of the apps.\n\n**4. User Responsibilities**\n\n4.1 You are solely responsible for the use of the Apps and for any consequences arising from such use.\n\n4.2 You represent and warrant that you have the legal right to access, use, and share the call history data processed by the Apps. \n\n4.3 You agree not to use the Apps for any illegal or unauthorized purposes, including but not limited to:\n    * Violating any local, national, or international law or regulation.\n    * Infringing upon the intellectual property rights of any third party.\n    * Transmitting any harmful content, including viruses, malware, or other destructive code.\n    * Attempting to gain unauthorized access to the Apps or their related systems.\n\n**5. Disclaimer of Warranties**\n\n5.1 THE APPS ARE PROVIDED \"AS IS\" AND \"AS AVAILABLE\" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. \n\n5.2 WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE APPS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE APPS ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.\n\n5.3 WE MAKE NO WARRANTY REGARDING THE SECURITY OF YOUR DATA WHILE IN TRANSIT OR STORED ON OUR SERVERS, AND WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY BREACH OF SECURITY OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO YOUR DATA.\n\n**6. Limitation of Liability**\n\nTO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO YOUR USE OF THE APPS, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.\n\n**7. Indemnification**\n\nYou agree to indemnify and hold harmless the developer of the apps from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses, costs, and expenses (including attorney\'s fees) arising out of or relating to: (i) your use of the Apps; (ii) your violation of these Terms; or (iii) your violation of any third-party rights.\n\n**8. Termination**\n\nWe may terminate your access to the Apps, in whole or in part, at any time and for any reason, without notice. \n\n**9. Entire Agreement**\n\nThese Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and the developer of the apps relating to the subject matter herein and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether oral or written.\n\n**10.  Changes to Terms**\n\nWe may update these Terms from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Terms on our website or within the Apps. Your continued use of the Apps after the posting of the updated Terms constitutes your acceptance of the changes. \n\n---\n\n## Privacy Policy for Num Sum\n\n** (\"we\", \"us\", or \"our\") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect your information when you use our mobile applications Num Sum (\"App\").**\n\n**1. Information We Collect** \n\n**1.1.  Call History Data:**\n* Num Sum collects and encrypts your device\'s call history, which includes phone numbers you call and receive calls from, contact name for the numbers, call duration, and call timestamps.\n\n**1.2. User Behavior Data:**\n* We use Firebase Analytics to collect data about how you interact with the Apps. This may include information such as features accessed, usage patterns, performance metrics, crashes, and other diagnostic data.\n\n**1.3. Device Information:**\n* We may collect information about your device, such as device model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information. \n\n**2. How We Use Your Information**\n\n**2.1. To Provide and Improve the Services:** \n* We use your information to enable the core functionality of the Apps, which is to synchronize call history between your devices.\n* We also use data to improve the Apps\' performance, troubleshoot issues, and develop new features.\n\n**2.2. Analytics and Research:** \n* We use anonymized, aggregated data to analyze trends, understand user behavior, and improve the user experience.\n\n**2.3. Personalized Advertising:**\n* The Apps display advertisements using Google AdMob. Google may collect and use data to personalize ad content. To learn more about Google\'s privacy practices and your choices, please visit Google\'s Privacy & Terms: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).\n\n**3. How We Share Your Information**\n\n**3.1. Service Providers:**\n* We may engage trusted third-party service providers to assist us in providing and improving the Apps (e.g., Firebase for data storage, Google AdMob for advertising). These providers are obligated to protect your data.\n\n**3.2. Legal Requirements:**\n* We may disclose your information if required by law or to comply with a valid legal process (e.g., a court order, search warrant, subpoena).\n* While we strive to cooperate with legitimate legal requests, we cannot decrypt the content of your call history data due to the encryption method employed. You are solely responsible for complying with any legal obligations related to providing access to your data.\n\n**4.  Data Security**\n\n* We use industry-standard encryption to protect your call history data during transmission and storage.\n* Access to data stored on Firebase Firestore is restricted to authorized personnel and protected by Firebase security rules. \n* However, no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security. \n\n**5. Data Retention**\n\n* Call history data is retained in Firebase Firestore for as long as you maintain an active account with the Apps.\n* To minimize potential security risks, call history data is deleted from Firebase Firestore once it has been successfully downloaded by the Call Sync app.\n* You can delete all your call history data from the cloud by signing out of the apps. \n\n**6. Children\'s Privacy**\n\n* The Apps are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. \n* We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.\n\n**7. Changes to This Privacy Policy**\n\n* We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. \n* We will post any changes on this page and provide notice within the Apps.]]></string>
    <string name="num_sum_app_logo">Num Sum App Logo</string>
    <string name="call_sync_name">Num Sum</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">lets you send Call History to your other Phone</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="connection2_desc">Scan the QR code using Call Sync app</string>
    <string name="dkma_title">Enable Background work</string>
    <string name="space_string">" "</string>
    <string name="dkma_error_dialog_message">We were unable to load the data from cloud. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="exit_app">Exit App</string>
    <string name="error_icon">Error Icon</string>
    <string name="dkma_dummy_explanation"><![CDATA[<div class=\"caution-box\">  8/2019 update  <br /><br />  <b>Good news</b>: HMD Global <a href=\"https://community.phones.nokia.com/discussion/51246/tapping-into-android-pies-adaptive-battery-for-optimum-battery-performance\">claims to disable Evenwell powersaving apps</a> on all devices running Android Pie or newer.  <br />  <b>NOT SO GOOD NEWS</b>: DuraSpeed remains.</div><p>HMD Global/Nokia was the main reason this website came to exist. They had the most aggressive app killers preinstalled on their phones.</p><p>There were three different app killing mechanisms:</p><ul>  <li><em>com.evenwell.powersaving.g3</em> on Android Pie for most Nokia phones - <strong>this one has been disabled since 8/2019 on devices running Pie or greater</strong></li>  <li><em>com.evenwell.emm</em> on Android Go (Oreo?) for Nokia 1 - <strong>probably still in the wild since HMD only disabled Evenwell apps for Pie or greater</strong></li>  <li><em>DuraSpeed</em> on Android Pie (build 00WW_3_180) for the US Nokia 3.1 (TA-1049, TA-1063) and Nokia 5.1 - <strong>this one is still in the wild</strong></li></ul><h3 id=\"most-nokia-phones-power-saver-aka-comevenwellpowersavingg3\">Most Nokia phones (Power saver AKA com.evenwell.powersaving.g3)</h3><div class=\"caution-box\">  The Evenwell Power saver *(com.evenwell.powersaving.g3)* has been disabled by HMD Global for devices running Pie or greater as of 8/2019.</div><p>The text below has been left here to preserve the detail and history of events.</p><p><del>Note: In Feb/March 2019, apparently on a few models distributed in Europe and US, the Evenwell Power Saver has been reworked to not kill the apps as aggressively, which largely resolves all issues for those models.</del></p><p><del>Nokia on Android O and P kills any background process including sleep tracking (or any other sport tracking) after 20 minutes if the screen is off. Also when killed all alarms are stopped which renders for example any alarm clock apps useless.</del></p><p><del>We have investigated this issue in details. We did even purchase a Nokia 6.1 to be able to reproduce the issue. The problem only occurs on Nokia devices with Android Pie. Nokia started to bundle a toxic app (package: com.evenwell.powersaving.g3 or com.evenwell.emm, name: Power saver) with their devices by some 3rd party company Evenwell. This app kills apps in the most brutal way we have seen so far among Android vendors.</del></p><p><del>Whitelisting apps from battery optimizations does not help! Evenwell kills even whitelisted apps.</del></p><p><del>What this non-standard app does is every process gets killed after 20 minutes regardless it is actually supposed to be running and doing a useful job for the user. Also alarms are not triggered. The aim is apparently to save your battery by rendering tracking apps and other apps that use background processing useless.</del></p><p><del>Moreover even third-party user visible alarms (alarm clock alarms) are not triggering properly on Nokia as foreground services cannot be started from background on Nokia. This is a serious issue unparalleled to any other vendor. We did not yet find a workaround for this :(. 3rd party alarms clock / calendars etc… won’t be realiable on Nokia.</del></p><p><del>You can read more on this issue here:<a href=\"https://community.phones.nokia.com/discussion/3428/background-service-killed-even-when-whitelisted\">https://community.phones.nokia.com/discussion/3428/background-service-killed-even-when-whitelisted</a></del></p><p>For fun investigative read about Evenwell, check out <a href=\"https://medium.com/@roundedeverett/who-is-nokia-cb24ecbc52a9\">Who is Nokia?</a></p><h3 id=\"nokia-1-comevenwellemm\">Nokia 1 (com.evenwell.emm)</h3><p>On Nokia 1 there is an alternative package that works very similar to what the com.evenwell.powersaving.g3 package is doing on the higher end models.</p><h3 id=\"nokia-31-and-51-duraspeed\">Nokia 3.1 and 5.1 (DuraSpeed)</h3><p>On Mediatek-based devices, HMD has baked in <a href=\"https://www.appbrain.com/app/duraspeed/com.mediatek.duraspeed\">DuraSpeed</a> as a system service. There is no user-facing control, or whitelist; this Mediatek-developed task killer terminates all background apps without prejudice.</p><p>DuraSpeed can be disabled through the global settings store, but this is a protected area of Android that can only be manipulated through adb, or an app that has been granted the <code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</code> permission (which must also be done with ADB). Additionally, the setting does not survive a reboot. Users can fix their devices themselves using an automation app (see “Solution for users”), or apps can request the <code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</code> permission and then cycle the flag on startup to kill DuraSpeed. Syncthing-Fork is one app that has <a href=\"https://github.com/Catfriend1/syncthing-android/wiki/Nokia-HMD-phone-preparations\">taken this approach</a>.</p><p>Unfortunately, there are <a href=\"https://forum.xda-developers.com/showpost.php?s=1f4fbd7602c2739781c1c5346bb06e36&amp;p=80157506&amp;postcount=7\">some</a> <a href=\"https://github.com/urbandroid-team/dont-kill-my-app/issues/57#issuecomment-534246709\">reports</a> that even this fix does not work.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="dkma_dummy_user_solution"><![CDATA[<h3 id=\"most-nokia-phones-power-saver-aka-comevenwellpowersavingg3\">Most Nokia phones (Power saver AKA com.evenwell.powersaving.g3)</h3><p>To fix this issue, please do the following:</p><ul>  <li>    <p>Go to <strong>Phone settings &gt; Apps &gt; See all apps</strong>.</p>  </li>  <li>    <p>Tap on the <strong>right top corner menu &gt; Show system</strong>.</p>  </li>  <li>    <p>Find <strong>Power saver</strong> app in the list, select it and <strong>Force close</strong>. It will remain stopped for a while, but will restart itself eventually.</p>  </li></ul><p>From now on, background apps should work normally and use the standard Android battery optimizations.</p><p>Still 3rd party alarm clocks or any task scheduling of foreground tasks at a particular time won’t work. <del>We do not have any solution for this at the moment</del> UPDATE: in our preliminary tests it seems that force stopping or uninstalling the <strong>Power saver</strong> app also fixes alarms and starting of foreground services, until the Power saver restarts.</p><p>Alternative solution for tech-savvy users:</p><h3 id=\"most-nokia-models\">Most Nokia models</h3><div class=\"caution-box\">  The Evenwell Power saver *(com.evenwell.powersaving.g3)* has been disabled by HMD Global for devices running Pie or greater as of 8/2019.</div><p>Disable the <em>com.evenwell.powersaving.g3</em> package via the following adb commands:</p><p><code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">adb shell</code><br /><code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">pm disable-user com.evenwell.powersaving.g3</code></p><h3 id=\"nokia-1-android-go\">Nokia 1 (Android Go)</h3><p>Disable the <em>com.evenwell.emm</em> package via the following adb commands:</p><p><code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">adb shell</code><br /><code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">pm disable-user com.evenwell.emm</code></p><h3 id=\"nokia-31-and-51\">Nokia 3.1 and 5.1</h3><p>Regrettably, HMD did not include any sort of Settings switch to control DuraSpeed’s operation. And since the task killer is a system service and not an app, it cannot simply be uninstalled. Fortunately, DuraSpeed does have a hidden kill switch: It watches the <code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">setting.duraspeed.enabled</code> setting and will stop itself when the flag is set to any value that does not equal <code class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\">1</code>. Once DuraSpeed stops itself, the phone is cured and all background apps will function normally. However, this workaround does not stick across reboots, so the flag has to be cycled at every boot using an automation app like <a href=\"https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.arlosoft.macrodroid\">MacroDroid</a>.</p><p>First, use adb to grant MacroDroid (or your choice of automation app) the ability to write to the global settings store:</p><div class=\"language-plaintext highlighter-rouge\"><div class=\"highlight\"><pre class=\"highlight\"><code>adb shell pm grant com.arlosoft.macrodroid android.permission.WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</code></pre></div></div><p>Then create a task, triggered at <strong>Device Boot</strong>, that performs the following:</p><ol>  <li>System Setting: type <strong>Global</strong>, name <strong>setting.duraspeed.enabled</strong>, value <strong>2</strong></li>  <li>System Setting: type <strong>System</strong>, name <strong>setting.duraspeed.enabled</strong>, value <strong>2</strong></li>  <li>System Setting: type <strong>Global</strong>, name <strong>setting.duraspeed.enabled</strong>, value <strong>0</strong></li>  <li>System Setting: type <strong>System</strong>, name <strong>setting.duraspeed.enabled</strong>, value <strong>0</strong></li></ol><p>NOTE: You need both ‘Global’ and ‘System’ type settings (the screenshots below show only Global - you get the idea).</p><div class=\"img-block\">  <figure>     <img src=\"https://dontkillmyapp.com/assets/img/nokia/duraspeed_macrodroid_kyrasantae.png\" />     <figcaption>MacroDroid example task</figcaption>  </figure>  <figure>     <img src=\"https://dontkillmyapp.com/assets/img/nokia/duraspeed_tasker_yoryan.jpg\" />     <figcaption>Tasker example task</figcaption>  </figure></div><p>Run this task and verify there are no errors. If all is well, then DuraSpeed will be immediately disabled, and it will also be disabled on reboot.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="test_user">Test User</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_explanation_part_1">"We need your Camera Permission to establish a secure connection with "</string>
    <string name="camer_permisssion_explanation_part_2">" app."</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_request_title">Camera Permission Required</string>
    <string name="allow_camera">Allow Camera</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="qr_code_scanner">QR Code Scanner</string>
    <string name="eula_document_link">https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vTxwjzfStLew5xtGLTJi6pgAhZhJifkIv1VQ02PFnpfwPXegZRWb73mlOuz8ndW_ki0SGNhyuAGngVx/pub</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_document_link">https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vSNLxqaP50939nMPCARWI_eIp7F4uzId4UjkX4vU2pdV5vchrGSIwkOQRlpJcnsvTJsE-jtYkz7szOw/pub</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_document_link">https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vQjOTONAXl_H6P8rk2tHVXWIdhAnWlRNYNnyIdojruM8lHO3Y77WAhsOpjVfLkESKJRsRVZ-5__GL3X/pub</string>
</resources>